{
  "decks": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "name": "Rendering in React",
      "description": "React's component structure allows for quickly building a complex web application that relies on DOM manipulation."
    },
    {
      "name": "React Router",
      "description": "React Router is a collection of navigational components that compose declaratively with your application.",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "name": "React Router3",
      "description": "React Router3 is a collection of navigational components that compose declaratively with your application.",
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "name": "pasta",
      "description": "ter",
      "id": 5
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "What path will match the follow Route?\n<Route>\n  <NotFound />\n</Route>vxcvxcv",
      "back": "All paths. A route with no path matches all URL'svxcvcxv",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "front": "What does <Switch> do?",
      "back": "Renders the first matching child <Route> ",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "front": "Differentiate between Real DOM and Virtual DOM3.",
      "back": "Virtual DOM updates are faster but do not directly update the HTML3",
      "deckId": 4
    },
    {
      "cards": [],
      "front": "bdxbcxb",
      "back": "bbxcvb",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "front": "awrijw",
      "back": "sorwa",
      "deckId": 5,
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "front": "esrtes",
      "back": "setrest",
      "deckId": 5,
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "front": "awtwatr",
      "back": "awfhgsfdy",
      "deckId": 5,
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "front": "aewr",
      "back": "awrawr",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "front": "",
      "back": "",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 13
    },
    {
      "front": "",
      "back": "",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 14
    },
    {
      "front": "",
      "back": "",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 15
    },
    {
      "front": "",
      "back": "",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 16
    },
    {
      "front": "",
      "back": "",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 18
    },
    {
      "front": "sdasd",
      "back": "sfdafd",
      "deckId": 5,
      "id": 19
    },
    {
      "front": "dsf",
      "back": "fasd",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 20
    },
    {
      "front": "asdf",
      "back": "fadsf",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 21
    },
    {
      "front": "",
      "back": "",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 22
    },
    {
      "front": "gfdg",
      "back": "dhgffdg",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 23
    },
    {
      "front": "ffsdfdsfds",
      "back": "sdfdsf",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 24
    }
  ]
}